Germer, Adolph Papers on Microfilm 5809 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Diaries, 1941-1945 (Reel 28)
  - 0198. Diary. Volume 11. 207 frames., 1942; 2 (Reel 28)
    Locations: Colorado, Wyoming, Oregon, Washington, Illinois, District of Columbia, Wisconsin, Minnesota, Montana, California, Utah, Nevada, Texas, Mexico, Michigan, Massachusetts, New York, Missouri, Tennessee, Arkansas.
  - 0405. Diary. Volume 12. 196 frames., 1943; 3 (Reel 28)
    Locations: Oregon, Washington, Colorado, Missouri, Illinois, Montana, California, Idaho, Utah, Ohio, Tennessee, Texas, Arkansas, Mississippi, District of Columbia, Nevada, Pennsylvania, New York, Wisconsin, Wyoming.
  - 0600. Diary. Volume 13. 188 frames., 1944; 4 (Reel 28)
    Locations: Oregon, Montana, Colorado, Utah, Illinois, Wisconsin, District of Columbia, Missouri, Nebraska, Washington, Iowa, Minnesota, Texas, Oklahoma, Arkansas, Michigan, British Columbia, Kentucky, Ohio.
  - 0788. Diary. Volume 14. 187 frames., 1945; 5 (Reel 28)
    Locations: Colorado, Texas, Oklahoma, Missouri, Illinois, District of Columbia, Pennsylvania, New York, Ohio, Minnesota, Nebraska, Iowa, Wisconsin, Montana, Utah, Washington, Oregon, California, Kentucky, Massachusetts, British Columbia, Manitoba.
- Diaries, 1946-1951 (Reel 29)
  - 0001. Diary. Volume 15. 174 frames., 1946; 1 (Reel 29)
    Locations: Illinois, Nebraska, Colorado, Montana, Utah, Wisconsin, Iowa, Minnesota, Missouri, Oklahoma, Arkansas, Tennessee, Texas, Ohio, California, Mexico, Oregon, Washington, District of Columbia, New Mexico, Virginia, West Virginia, Quebec, Nova Scoti
  - 0175. Diary. Volume 16. 182 frames., 1947; 2 (Reel 29)
    Locations: Illinois, District of Columbia, New York, Great Britain, France, Germany, Senegal, Czechoslovakia, New Jersey, Ohio, Kentucky, West Virginia, Colorado, Utah, Oregon, Massachusetts, Wisconsin, Nebraska, Minnesota, Wyoming, California, Washington
  - 0357. Diary. Volume 17. 193 frames., 1948; 3 (Reel 29)
    Locations: Illinois, District of Columbia, Nebraska, Colorado, Utah, Oregon, California, British Columbia, Washington, Iowa, Minnesota, Pennsylvania, Michigan, Wisconsin, Massachusetts, New York, Wyoming.
  - 0550. Diary. Volume 18. 190 frames., 1949; 4 (Reel 29)
    Locations: Illinois, California, Oregon, Washington, British Columbia, Utah, Colorado, District of Columbia, Wisconsin, Minnesota, Nebraska, Ohio, Wyoming.
  - 0740. Diary. Volume 19. 177 frames., 1950; 5 (Reel 29)
    Locations: Illinois, Oregon, Washington, British Columbia, California, Utah, Colorado, Nebraska, Ontario, Michigan, Wyoming, Idaho, District of Columbia, Montana, Minnesota, Mississippi, Georgia, Alabama.
  - 0917. Diary. Volume 20. 188 frames., 1951; 6 (Reel 29)
    Locations: Illinois, District of Columbia, Ohio, Michigan, Colorado, Wyoming, Oregon, Utah, New York, Minnesota, Wisconsin, Tennessee, Quebec, Pennsylvania, Arizona, California, Missouri, Nebraska, Iowa.
- Diaries, 1952-1958 (Reel 30)
  - 0001. Diary. Volume 21. 193 frames., 1952; 1 (Reel 30)
    Locations: Oregon, Washington, Utah, Colorado, Wyoming, California, Illinois, Idaho, District of Columbia, New York, Ohio, Pennsylvania, New Jersey, Wisconsin, Minnesota.
  - 0194. Diary. Volume 22. 189 frames., 1953; 2 (Reel 30)
    Locations: Illinois, Iowa, Nebraska, Minnesota, Colorado, Wyoming, Utah, Oregon, Washington, California, Mexico, District of Columbia, Michigan, Pennsylvania, North Carolina, Ohio, New York, New Jersey, Virginia, British Columbia, Idaho.
  - 0383. Diary. Volume 23. 1954 Part 1. 14 Frames., 3 (Reel 30)
    Locations: Minnesota, Montana, Wyoming, Colorado.
  - 0397. Diary. Volume 24. 1954 Part 2. 189 frames., 4 (Reel 30)
    Locations: Illinois, District of Columbia, New Jersey, New York, Wisconsin, Colorado, Wyoming, Oregon, Idaho, Washington, British Columbia, California, Minnesota, Montana, Utah, Puerto Rico, United States Virgin Islands, Missouri.
  - 0586. Diary. Volume 25. 190 frames., 1955; 5 (Reel 30)
    Locations: Illinois, Minnesota, Michigan, Wisconsin, Georgia, District of Columbia, New York, Massachusetts, Rhode Island, Alabama, Tennessee, Ohio, Missouri, Louisiana, Oregon, California, Arkansas, Washington
  - 0776. Diary. Volume 26. 94 frames., 1956; 6 (Reel 30)
    Locations: Illinois, Oregon, Ontario, Wisconsin.
  - 0870. Diary. Volume 27. 52 frames., 1957; 7 (Reel 30)
    Locations: Illinois, New Jersey, New York, Georgia, Michigan, Ohio.
  - 0922. Diary. Volume 28. 32 frames., 1958; 8 (Reel 30)
    Locations: Illinois, Tennessee, Kentucky, California.
  - 0954. Scrapbook. News clippings. 101 frames., 1930-1964; 9 (Reel 30)
    1930-1964 and Undated